Gaming
unityractor
Let Show
arectorstationscreen Max pannel
Place Text object and Cold stats text
zancreatity New text paranted to that
stats text
encolate Stat textviller
This textvilion Action Number of
bigos It's parent a to the stats text
if you move it Around it you Follow You
stats text
Good Set The Enter of the Start Text to
be Top Left
okuit notstats and coses object will be
showing the value of your attribute
Create necessary  newscript Code corrector A3
text
you Steam Pro Library
Creta serialistfield Cold wellow text
reference atribute textvalue in the
Editor
Inside Create Public Method Cold update
text
disabled Past The wello watch The One to
show it The textfield
sollects goback to the Editor andreate
Fields For echop The carector atribute
babyfapping Text and duplicating it on
the Screen
Good not to armain objectless from the status of the
Panama component and kchcholi Lets changite a
little Creta New  component Cold status
Manager
This component wildberriesponse was  For
managing the status pannel on the screen.
When to show it, select
the corrector on it to be shown. The
status pannel component and both
often appear on it.
The status pannel. Solid move.
Everything accordant. The Change.
Let's Finish. The status on new ze. Sin.
Remember. But you. Heaven name nhp. Bar.
Onet in our Main sin x objects to the
level Up sin status Pana
Good
on decreasing not topdeys attribute. Text on
the screen accordin to the Past caregiver
to be shown on the screen in the status pane. Create
Field for Strange Magic and
attributes to does. Faster you can use
Control. Deto duplicate. The Line update.
Text of the attribute
parameter tomackit shorter en More Clear
manager in herve. One to into Fix
selected corrector you want fix here
corrector also he for the status pane. First
Lets extract. The Mouse Hover over object.
Part broke out. Alex. The carector
fourstatus pannel. Base on the Mouse
Activity
Good.
The carector Bull and serialis the
carector
simplect for the status pane. If aur  setting
of the status pano is Fix carrector
Now If & Set The status panoproperley
display isod our status pannel Reflex
The stats of the carector
good good
effevenications level